Washington Square Contemporary Music Society 1973-2013 MSS 390
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Audio
  - Subseries B: Originals
    - Hoffman - Numbers; Stravinsky - Serenade in A; Eckardt - Tangled Loops, December 1, 1998 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0112)
    - "And All is Always Now" - Bruce Adolphe (1992), March 22, 1999 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0113)
    - Adolphe, Fennelly, Karchin, Keriger (1 of 2) Master, March 22, 1999 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0114)
    - Greenbaum, Gao Weijie, Stravinsky (2 of 2) Master, March 22, 1999 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0115)
    - American Brass: Starer, Ives, Druckman, Fennelly, Sampson, encore, March, 2000 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0116)
    - WSCMS and Talujon Percussion Quartet, March 20, 2001 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0117)
    - WSCMC - Whole concert (1 of 2), October 15, 2001 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0118)
    - WSCMC - Whole concert (2 of 2), October 15, 2001 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0119)
    - Merkin Concert Hall (1 of 2), March 26, 2003 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0120)
    - Merkin Concert Hall (2 of 2), March 26, 2003 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0121)
    - WSCMS (1 of 2), March 26, 2003 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0122)
    - WSCMS (2 of 2), March 26, 2003 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0123)
    - Rolf Schulte, James Winn (1 of 2), December 9, 2003 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0124)
    - Rolf Schulte, James Winn (2 of 2), December 9, 2003 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0125)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall concert (1 of 2), December 2, 2004 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0126)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall concert (2 of 2), December 2, 2004 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0127)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall concert (1 of 2), March 9, 2005 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0128)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall concert (2 of 2), March 9, 2005 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0129)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall concert (1 of 2), October 20, 2005 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0130)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall concert (2 of 2), October 20, 2005 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0131)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall concert (1 of 2), December 5, 2005 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0132)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall concert (2 of 2), December 5, 2005 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0133)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall concert - Gen'ei no Mai, Tribute, Six Miniatures, Duo Capriccioso, Wood Forms, A Three Piece Suite: Sout of the Blue, The Sunlight Thins, The View Empties; Gauntlet, December 5, 2005 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0134)
    - WSCMS (unlabeled), December 5, 2005 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0135)
    - A Salute to Milton Babbitt at 90 (1 of 2), April 3, 2006 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0136)
    - A Salute to Milton Babbitt at 90 (2 of 2), April 3, 2006 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0137)
    - Songlines (Martin Boykan), April 3, 2006 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0138)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall concert (1 of 2), April 3, 2006 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0139)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall concert (2 of 2), April 3, 2006 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0140)
    - ICE - deLeon - Trembling Time; Nicolaw - Prisma; Papavasilopolus - Pasa Pnoi; Hermentin - Nonett; Rua - Concerto #3, October 18, 2006 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0141)
    - Avalon Quartet - Biggs; Fennelly, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0142)
    - Avalon Quartet: Quayle - Sweet Insanity; Schoenberg - String Quartet #2, December 14, 2006 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0143)
    - Brooklyn Conservatory - New Music Collective and WSCMS, March 7, 2008 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0144)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall concert (1 of 2), March 10, 2008 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0145)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall concert (2 of 2), March 10, 2008 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0146)
    - Sagala, Martin, Richardson, Taub, Mei-Fang Lin, May 5, 2008 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0147)
    - Kreiger, Kilstofte, Fennelly - Tropes and Echoes, May 5, 2008 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0148)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall concert (1 of 2), October 2, 2008 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0149)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall concert (2 of 2), October 2, 2008 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0150)
    - The Either/Or Ensemble, March 26, 2009 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0151)
    - The Either/Or Ensemble, March 26, 2009 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0152)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall concert - Season 33, December 3, 2009 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0153)
    - Machant; [Dzubay]; Lara; Pintscher; Ness; Browning, March 3, 2010 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0154)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall Concert - Rehearsal, April 7, 2001 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0155)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall Concert - Rehearsal, April 7, 2010 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0156)
    - WSCMS Merkin Hall Concert - Season 33, April 7, 2010 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0157)
    - WSCMS, March 24, 2011 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0158)
    - East Coast Contemporary Ensemble - Tenri Cultural Institute, March 24, 2011 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0159)
    - East Coast Contemporary Ensemble - Tenri Cultural Institute, March 24, 2011 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0160)
    - East Coast Contemporary Ensemble - Tenri Cultural Institute, March 24, 2011 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0161)
    - Talea Ensemble - American Crosscurrents, March 24, 2011 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0162)
    - Talea Ensemble - American Crosscurrents, March 24, 2011 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0163)
    - Washington Square Ensemble, April 6, 2011 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0164)
    - Washington Square Ensemble - Muses at Play, April 6, 2011 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0165)
    - Washington Square Ensemble - Muses at Play, April 6, 2011 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0166)
    - Washington Square Ensemble, 35th Season, Concert 1, December 16, 2011 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0167)
    - Washington Square Ensemble, 35th Season, Concert 1, December 16, 2011 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0168)
    - Washington Square Ensemble, 35th Season, Concert 1, December 16, 2011 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0169)
    - WSCMS and Counter Induction, October 20, 2012 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0170)
    - WSCMS and Counter Induction, October 20, 2012 (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0171)
    - Lennon, Jaffe, Chasalow, Dello Joio, Undated (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0172)
    - [AGON], Undated (Box 6, Media ID: 390.0173)
  - Subseries C: Papers Removed from Media
    - Papers removed from 390.0006, 390.0007, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Papers removed from 390.0008, 390.0010, 390.0012, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Papers removed from 390.0013, 390.0015, 390.0016, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Papers removed from 390.0017, 390.0018, 390.0020, 390.0021, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Papers removed from 390.0022, 390.0024, 390.0025, 390.0026, 390.0027, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Papers removed from 390.0028, 390.0029, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Papers removed from 390.0034, 390.0036, 390.0038, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Papers removed from 390.0041, 390.0042, 390.0043, 390.0044, 390.0045, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Papers removed from 390.0046, 390.0048, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Papers removed from 390.0147, 390.148, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Papers removed from 390.0163, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Papers removed from media (loose in box), 1994, 1996, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 12)